Correctional Association of New York; Records apap014
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED], 1942-1960; 1962-1988; 1970-1986; 1; 9.33 cubic ft.
  - Board of Directors - Mailings [RESTRICTED], 1974-1978 (Box 2 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors - Mailings [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 2 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
    Includes Meeting Minutes.
  - Board of Directors - Mailings [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 2 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors - Mailings [RESTRICTED], 1980-1981 (Box 2 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors - Mailings [RESTRICTED], 1980-1982 (Box 2 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
    Includes Meeting Minutes. Contains items housed in oversized materials folder.
  - Board of Directors - Mailings [RESTRICTED], 1980-1982 (Box 2 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors - Mailings [RESTRICTED], 1981-1984 (Box 2 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Board of Directors - Mailings [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 2 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors - Mailings [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 2 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Board of Directors Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 2 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Board of Directors - Reports to [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 2 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Board of Directors - Standing Committees [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Box 2 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Brochure Ideas [RESTRICTED], 1971-1982 (Box 2 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Budgets [RESTRICTED], 1973-1976 (Box 2 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
    Contains items housed in oversized material folder.
  - Budgets [RESTRICTED], 1973-1976 (Box 2 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Budgets [RESTRICTED], 1977-1982 (Box 2 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
    Contains items housed in oversized material folder and in flat file.
  - Budgets [RESTRICTED], 1977-1982 (Box 2 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Building Committee [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 2 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - Building file [RESTRICTED], 1976-1984 (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - OS Capital Construction [RESTRICTED], 1976-1978; 1980-1984 (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
    Workhouse of the City of New York, Riker's Island, 1958 and Adolescent Remand Center, Brooklyn, 1961.
  - Carey-Harding Material [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Capital Punishment - Volker Graber Bill [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Chase Manhattan Bank [RESTRICTED], 1981-1984 (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Citibank [RESTRICTED], 1968-1982 (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Committee on Future Policy [RESTRICTED], 1967-1972 (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Committee on Future Policy [RESTRICTED], 1967-1972 (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Committee on Institutions and Offender Services [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Conferences - Gangi, Robert [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Constitution and Bylaws [RESTRICTED], 1976; 1981-1982 (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Constitution and Bylaws Committee [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Contribution Breakdowns [RESTRICTED], 1972-1975 (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Correctional Association History [RESTRICTED], 1955-1983 (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Correctional Association Legislative Mandate [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Correctional Association Office [RESTRICTED], 1983-1986 (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Correctional Association Staff [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Correctional Association - Staff Media [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Attorneys [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert [RESTRICTED], 1982; 2 folders (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19-20)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert [RESTRICTED], 1983; 3 folders (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21-23)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert [RESTRICTED], 1984; 2 folders (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24-25)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert [RESTRICTED], 1985; 3 folders (Box 3 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26-28)
    Contains a letter from Jean Harris concerning drug addition rates among prisoners; Contains items housed in oversized material folder.
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert, Outgoing [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert, Outgoing [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert/Board of Directors [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert/Dean, William [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert/Mushlin, Michael [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Gangi, Robert/Powers, Susan [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - General [RESTRICTED], 1965-1976 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - General [RESTRICTED], 1971-1974 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - General [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - General [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - General [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - General [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - General [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - General [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - General [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - Inmates [RESTRICTED], 1970-1972 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - Inmates [RESTRICTED], 1973-1976 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - Inmates [RESTRICTED], 1977-1982 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - Inmates [RESTRICTED], 1980-1981 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - Inmates [RESTRICTED], 1982-1986 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Correspondence - Inmates - Attica Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - Inmates - Fishkill Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1976-1979 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence - Inmates - Form Letter Responses [RESTRICTED], 1981-1984 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Correspondence - Inmates - Green Meadow Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Correspondence - Inmates - Stormville Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1976-1985 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - Correspondence - Inmates - Wallkill Correctional Facility [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - Correspondence - McQuillan, Adam F. (President) [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - Correspondence - McQuillan, Adam F. [RESTRICTED], 1978; 2 folders (Box 4 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28-29)
  - Correspondence - McQuillan, Adam F., President [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - McQuillan, Adam F., President [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Media [RESTRICTED], 1980-1981 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Media - Daily News [RESTRICTED], 1982-1986 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - Media - Newsday [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - Media - Newsday [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Correspondence - Media - New York Times [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - Media - Print [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - Media - Television [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Media - Village Voice [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - Membership [RESTRICTED], 1982-1984 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - New York City Board of Correction [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978; 1982; 1984 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - New York City Council [RESTRICTED], 1982-1984 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - New York City Office of the Mayor [RESTRICTED], 1976-1984 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
    Contains signed letters from Mayor Edward Koch.
  - Correspondence - New York State Attorney General [RESTRICTED], 1977-1983 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - New York State Board of Parole [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - New York State Commission of Correction [RESTRICTED], 1978-1987 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - New York State Comptroller [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - New York State Department of Correctional Services [RESTRICTED], 1982-1984 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - New York State Department of Criminal Justice [RESTRICTED], 1982-1984 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Correspondence - New York State Legislature [RESTRICTED], 1971-1974 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - New York State Legislature [RESTRICTED], 1975-1979 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence - New York State Legislature [RESTRICTED], 1981-1985 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Correspondence - New York State Legislature [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Correspondence - New York State Legislature - Marino, Ralph [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - Correspondence - New York State Sentencing Guidelines Committee [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - Correspondence - Pachoda, Dan (President) [RESTRICTED], 1979-1982 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - Correspondence - Pachoda, Dan (President) - Pretrial Release Study [RESTRICTED], 1980-1981 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
  - Correspondence - Requests for Information [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
  - Correspondence - U.S. Congress [RESTRICTED], 1970-1975 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
    Contains letters from Representatives Edward I. Koch, William F. Ryan, and Lester L. Woolf and Senators Birch Bayh and Jacob K. Javits.
  - Correspondence - US Department of Justice [RESTRICTED], 1980-1983 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
  - Correspondence - Walker, George G. (Chairman) [RESTRICTED], 1977-1982 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
  - Correspondence - Walker, George G. [RESTRICTED], 1977-1982 (Box 5 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
  - Correspondence - Wallkill Branch NAACP [RESTRICTED], 1984-1987 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Walsh, Marna (Board Secretary) [RESTRICTED], 1973-1980 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Walsh, Marna [RESTRICTED], 1973-1980 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - Walsh, Marna [RESTRICTED], 1973-1980 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - White Street Jail [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Correspondence - White Street Jail [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Criminal Justice Policies [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Criminal Justice Policies [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Dean, William T. (Chairman of the Board) [RESTRICTED], 1976-1985 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Death Penalty Legislation - Testimony [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Endowment Restrictions [RESTRICTED], 1948-1975 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Endowment Restrictions [RESTRICTED], 1948-1975 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee - Guest Speakers [RESTRICTED], 1962-1971 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Federal Work Study Program (College) [RESTRICTED], 1971-1975 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Finance Committee [RESTRICTED], 1961-1973 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Finance Committee [RESTRICTED], 1963-1973 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Finance Committee [RESTRICTED], 1976-1982 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Finance Committee [RESTRICTED], 1977-1982 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Financial Statements [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Financial Statements [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Fourth Floor Certificate of Occupancy - Kenneth Ricci, Architect [RESTRICTED], 1974-1977 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - Friedlander, Shelley - Resume [RESTRICTED], Undated (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - Gangi, Robert - Appointment as Executive Director [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - Gangi, Robert - Speeches [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 28)
  - Kates, Erika [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 29)
  - Lasker Reception [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 30)
  - Lasker Reception [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 31)
  - Lasker Reception - Invitations [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 32)
  - Law Committee [RESTRICTED], 1970-1980 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 33)
  - Law Committee [RESTRICTED], 1970-1980 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 34)
  - Law Committee [RESTRICTED], 1970-1980 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 35)
  - Law Committee [RESTRICTED], 1970-1980 (Box 6 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 36)
  - Law Committee - Buchanan Case [RESTRICTED], 1969-1970 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Legislative Memoranda [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Legislative Proposals [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - Legislative Recommendations [RESTRICTED], 1969-1977 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - Legislative Recommendations [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - Legislative Recommendations [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - Legislative Recommendations [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - Legislative Recommendations [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - Legislative Recommendations [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - Legislative Recommendations [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Legislative Recommendations [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Liman Commission Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Long Island Correctional Facility Closure - Press Releases [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - McKay Reception [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - McKay Reception [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - McKay Reception - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - McKay Reception - Invitations [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Media Contacts [RESTRICTED], 1980; 1982-1983 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Membership [RESTRICTED], 1975-1982 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Membership and Media Committee [RESTRICTED], 1974-1978 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Membership and Media Committee [RESTRICTED], 1974-1978 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Membership Mailings [RESTRICTED], 1976-1981 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Membership Mailings [RESTRICTED], 1982-1985 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Membership Meetings [RESTRICTED], 1984-1989 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Membership Questionnaire [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - Membership Statistics [RESTRICTED], 1976-1980 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - Membership Statistics [RESTRICTED], 1981-1984 (Box 7 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1982-1987 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 1)
  - Morgan Guaranty Trust Co. [RESTRICTED], 1971-1980 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 2)
  - Newsletter Master Copies [RESTRICTED], 1968-1980 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 3)
  - New York City Council [RESTRICTED], 1983-1985 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 4)
  - New York State Budget Information Requests [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 5)
  - New York State Charities Registration [RESTRICTED], 1975-1983 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 6)
  - New York State legislation - Governor's Proposed [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 7)
  - New York State Recidivism [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 8)
  - New York State Sentencing Guidelines [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 9)
  - New York State Sentencing Guidelines [RESTRICTED], 1984-1985 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 10)
  - Nominating Committee [RESTRICTED], 1963-1972 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 11)
  - Nominating Committee [RESTRICTED], 1974-1984 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 12)
  - Patterson Affair Follow-up [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 13)
  - Patterson Affair - Resources Committee [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 14)
  - Patterson Affair - Working Lists [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 15)
  - Phoenix Mutual Life Insurance [RESTRICTED], 1977-1980 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 16)
  - Press/Broadcast Contacts [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 17)
  - Press Releases [RESTRICTED], 1962-1976 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 18)
  - Press Releases [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 19)
  - Price of Punishment - Executive Summary [RESTRICTED], 1982 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 20)
  - Prison Construction - Press Release [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 21)
  - Prison Mental Health Committee [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 22)
  - Prison Mental Health Committee - Correspondence [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 23)
  - Prison Visits - Brooklyn House of Detention Affidavits [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 24)
  - Prison Visits - Queens House of Detention [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 25)
  - Prison Visits - Queens House of Detention [RESTRICTED], 1975-1978 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 26)
  - Prison Visits - The Tombs [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 8 (1-Board of Directors Files [RESTRICTED]), Folder 27)